So I'm here at the airport and I see this woman who had this cute jacket and it was like a cargo jacket, but the print was in pink and it had Jewish girl, Jewish girl all over the jacket.
And then I'm over here standing next to her with my cafe on, right?
And let me tell you why you always got to just stay true to who you are and your heart.
Because the way that some people who are Zionists are behaving is that they are sending a message out that there is anti-Semitism simply just because you are standing for Palestinians.
And what happens when people do that is it makes you then start wondering, are people looking at me a certain way, which then makes you look at someone a certain way.
And I said, Amanda, get all that noise out your head. You know what it is.
And what it is, is that I have had so many lovely Jewish folks in my life and I also just simply don't harbor hatred like that.
And I also don't assume that people harbor hatred like that because I don't want to live in a world like that.
So I start everybody with a blank fresh slate and guess what? We ended up in the same line and she was like, I love your work.
And I said, I love your jacket. And we said, have a safe flight.
And that's where we start. We always start at simply who we are as humans.
And then we work from there. Don't let these people, anybody in this world, give you the noise that they have not been able to silence with their hearts.
Thank you.